gamingzion.com 2015-06-12

# Privacy policy | GamingZion

Gaming Zion may occasionally collect non-personal and non-identifying information from our visitors. This information includes, but is not limited to: browser type and geographic location. Other, personally-identifiable information is only collected when visitors ask to be sent periodic emails (newsletter). In this situation, the personal information we collect is limited to the email address which you provide. Further personal information may be requested at certain times, but you will be made aware of our intentions at the time the information is collected. Sharing this information is optional, and users may choose to visit our site anonymously.

The information we collect from you may be used to personalize your experience, to administer promotions or other site features, or to send out occasional/periodic emails. Users who choose to subscribe to our newsletter and supply us with their email address will only receive solicited mailings, and their email address will never be used for sending un-solicited information or for direct marketing purposes. If at any time you wish to stop receiving emails, you may unsubscribe from the subscriptions page of our website. 

Gaming Zion may use cookies - small information files that are stored on your computer, enabling the site to recognize you. Gaming Zion uses cookies to remember your preferences and usage history for future visits, including but not limited to comments and ratings posted in certain areas of the Gaming Zion website. Some third party websites that feed ads onto Gaming zion may use their own cookies for their own purposes. Users who prefer not to accept cookies from our website should consult the documentation supplied with their web browser for information on how to manage cookies.

Gaming Zion will never sell, trade, or otherwise transfer any personal data we collect to outside parties. 

Gaming Zion may include links to third party products and services. These third party sites have their own privacy policies and terms of use. Gaming Zion has no responsibility or liability for the content of these linked sites. Nonetheless we welcome any feedback about the sites and services we link to.

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy. If at any time we make changes to this privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. Should you have other questions or concerns about this privacy policy, please do not hesitate to contact us.

 ** _Terms and Conditions_**  
Gaming Zion does not promote illegal or underage gambling, or gambling in jurisdictions where gambling or online gambling is considered unlawful. The information we offer on this site is provided for entertainment purposes only. Gaming Zion is not responsible for the content any published links. Gaming Zion is not responsible for any financial loss or damages you may incur. By using this site you agree that you are aware of these terms, that you are of legal gambling age, and that you live in an area where it is not unlawful to gamble or gamble online.
